<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Responsi 1 Mobile (H1D023075)</string>
    <string name="name">Bayer 04 Leverkusen</string>
    <string name="description">Bayer 04 Leverkusen, known as Die Werkself (The Company\'s Eleven), is a professional German football club based in Leverkusen, North Rhine-Westphalia. Founded in 1904 by employees of pharmaceutical company Bayer, the club competes in the Bundesliga and plays its home matches at the BayArena. Often nicknamed \'Neverkusen\' for their tendency to finish as runners-up in major competitions. Their colors are red and black, and they regularly compete in European competitions as one of Germany\'s top-tier clubs.</string>
    <string name="history">Club History</string>
    <string name="history_title">Bayer 04 Leverkusen\'s History</string>
    <string name="history_desc">Bayer 04 Leverkusen, affectionately known as Die Werkself (The Company\'s Eleven), stands as one of the most fascinating and unique institutions in German football. Founded on July 1, 1904, by employees of the pharmaceutical giant Bayer AG in Leverkusen, North Rhine-Westphalia, the club has maintained an inseparable bond with its corporate parent for over a century, making it one of the few professionally run company-sponsored clubs in modern football that is exempt from Germany\'s strict 50+1 ownership rule.\n\n

The club plays its home matches at the BayArena, a modern, purpose-built stadium with a capacity of approximately 30,210 spectators. Originally opened in 1958 and significantly renovated in the late 1990s, the BayArena is renowned for its intimate atmosphere and close proximity of fans to the pitch, creating an electric environment on matchdays. The stadium\'s sleek design and excellent facilities reflect the club\'s professional approach and corporate backing, making it one of the most well-maintained venues in German football.\n\n

Despite never winning a Bundesliga title, Leverkusen has established itself as a perennial contender in German football\'s elite tier. The club\'s most heartbreaking season came in 2001-02 when they finished as runners-up in the Bundesliga, DFB-Pokal, and UEFA Champions League—a treble of near-misses that earned them the unfortunate nickname \"Neverkusen\" or \"Vizekusen\" (Vice-kusen). This moniker has haunted the club through multiple runner-up finishes, though it also speaks to their consistent competitiveness at the highest level. Leverkusen has won the DFB-Pokal once (1993) and the UEFA Cup once (1988), while also claiming several DFB-Ligapokal and DFB-Supercup titles.\n\n

Bayer Leverkusen has cultivated a reputation as one of Europe\'s premier talent factories, with a world-class youth academy that has produced numerous international stars. The club is known for its commitment to attractive, attacking football with an emphasis on technical ability, quick transitions, and tactical flexibility. Over the decades, Leverkusen has been home to legendary players including Rudi Völler, Bernd Schuster, Michael Ballack, Lúcio, Arturo Vidal, Son Heung-min, and Kai Havertz, among many others. The club\'s scouting network extends globally, identifying young talent before they reach their peak and developing them into world-class performers.\n\n

Leverkusen is a regular participant in European competitions, having qualified for the UEFA Champions League and Europa League numerous times throughout their history. Their run to the Champions League final in 2002, though ending in defeat to Real Madrid, remains a highlight of the club\'s European adventures. The club\'s consistent presence in continental competition has helped establish Leverkusen as a respected name across Europe and has provided a platform for their talented squads to shine on the biggest stages.\n\n

The club\'s distinctive red and black colors reflect both their corporate heritage and their bold, aggressive style of play. While Leverkusen doesn\'t have the same deep-rooted local rivalries as some traditional clubs due to their corporate origins, they maintain a competitive regional rivalry with FC Cologne in the Rhine derby. Their matches against other top Bundesliga sides like Bayern Munich, Borussia Dortmund, and Borussia Mönchengladbach are always fiercely contested affairs.\n\n

In recent years, under the guidance of various progressive coaches and a forward-thinking management structure, Leverkusen has continued to evolve and compete for domestic and European honors. The club\'s financial stability, courtesy of Bayer AG\'s support, combined with smart recruitment and excellent player development, positions them as perpetual contenders for Champions League qualification and occasional challengers for the Bundesliga title. While the \"Neverkusen\" tag still lingers, the club\'s unwavering ambition is to finally capture that elusive Bundesliga championship and establish themselves among Germany\'s absolute elite, breaking free from the runner-up reputation once and for all.\n\n

Bayer 04 Leverkusen represents a unique blend of corporate professionalism, footballing excellence, and youth development that has carved out a special place in the German football landscape—a club that may not boast the most silverware, but commands respect through consistent quality, attacking entertainment, and an unwavering commitment to developing the stars of tomorrow.

    </string>
    <string name="head_coach">Head Coach</string>
    <string name="squad">Team Squad</string>
</resources>